<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<translations>
    <string id="page_title">Joan Prenafeta | Cool portfolio</string>
    <string id="page_title_aboutMe">About me | Joan Prenafeta | Cool portfolio</string>
    <string id="page_title_projects">Projects | Joan Prenafeta | Cool portfolio</string>
    <string id="skip_to_main_content">Skip to main content</string>
    <string id="header_site_logo_title">Go to the main page</string>
    <string id="nav_projects">Projects</string>
    <string id="nav_projects_title">Go to the projects section</string>
    <string id="nav_skills">Skills</string>
    <string id="nav_skills_title">Go to the skills section</string>
    <string id="nav_about_me">About me</string>
    <string id="nav_about_me_title">Go to the about me section</string>
    <string id="nav_awesome_tools_title">Go to the Awesome-tools tool. Opens in a new tab</string>
    
    <string id="lang_ca_title">Català</string>
    <string id="lang_es_title">Castellano</string>
    <string id="lang_en_title">English</string>

    <string id="main_h1_sr_only">Joan Prenafeta's portfolio.</string>
    <string id="splash_greeting">Hello, I'm Joan Prenafeta, a</string>
    <string id="splash_role_uxui">UX&amp;UI designer</string>
    <string id="splash_intro_part_2">who loves creating the best experiences for all kinds of users. Oh! By the way, I'm also a</string>
    <string id="splash_role_frontend">Front-end programmer</string>
    <string id="splash_avatar_aria">Joan Prenafeta in a pixel-art style</string>
    
    <string id="projects_title">Projects</string>
    <string id="projects_description">I cannot disclose the projects I've worked on. But here are my main tasks.</string>
    
    <string id="project_accessibility_name">Accessibility check</string>
    <string id="project_accessibility_description">I have performed several checks to ensure that websites comply with WCAG guidelines</string>

    <string id="project_uxui_name">UX&amp;UI design and layout</string>
    <string id="project_uxui_description">I have designed some of the most important public institution websites, reaching up to 100,000 monthly visitors.</string>
    
    <string id="project_programming_name">Programming</string>
    <string id="project_programming_description">I have worked as both a front-end and back-end programmer on different software systems for managing hospitals and veterinary clinics.</string>
    
    <string id="skills_title">What can I do?</string>
    <string id="skills_description">Some of my skills include:</string>
    <string id="skill_uxui">UX/UI Design</string>
    <string id="skill_frontend">Front-end</string>
    <string id="skill_accessibility">Accessibility</string>
    <string id="skill_scrum">SCRUM</string>
    <string id="skill_teamwork">Teamwork</string>

    <string id="about_me_img_alt">Portrait of Joan Prenafeta</string>
    <string id="about_me_title">Who am I?</string>
    <string id="about_me_p1_part1">I am a</string>
    <string id="about_me_p1_role">UX/UI designer</string>
    <string id="about_me_p1_part2">with front-end development experience. I previously worked as a Full Stack developer, although I was always more drawn to the</string>
    <string id="about_me_p1_frontend_bold">front-end</string>
    <string id="about_me_p1_part3">, especially UX/UI design. That's why I decided to specialize, and now I have several years of experience creating intuitive and attractive user experiences.</string>
    <string id="about_me_p2">My technical background and development experience allow me to deeply understand how designs translate into functional code and vice versa.</string>
    <string id="about_me_p3">Did you like what you've read so far? Great! Because I can offer much more. Don't hesitate to get in touch!</string>
    <string id="about_me_btn_know_more">Know more about me</string>
    <string id="about_me_btn_know_more_title">Go to the page about Joan. Opens in the same tab.</string>
    <string id="about_me_btn_message">Send me a message</string>
    <string id="about_me_btn_message_title">Send a message via LinkedIn</string>

    <string id="footer_last_update">Last updated: December 2025</string>
    <string id="footer_social_heading">My social networks</string>

    <string id="toggle_theme_sr_only">Toggle between light and dark mode</string>
    <string id="go_top">Return to top on this page</string>

    <string id="about_me_p1_full">I am a &lt;strong&gt;UX/UI designer&lt;/strong&gt; with front-end development experience. I previously worked as a Full Stack developer, although I was always more drawn to the &lt;strong&gt;front-end&lt;/strong&gt;, especially UX/UI design. That's why I decided to specialize, and now I have several years of experience creating intuitive and attractive user experiences.</string>
    <string id="about_me">About me</string>

    <string id="whyToan_title">Why &lt;strong&gt;TOAN&lt;/strong&gt;?</string>
    <string id="whyToan_p1">The naming of my professional brand is Toan. This choice is not arbitrary, but is based on a personal and emotional bond that directly reinforces my brand's philosophy: trust and accompaniment throughout the process. Toan is not a random invention, but a word with a deep and personal emotional charge. Its origin dates back to my childhood, when I had difficulty pronouncing the letter 'J' and referred to myself as "Toan" instead of "Joan". This small peculiarity became an affectionate nickname used by my closest loved ones, a symbol of unconditional support and acceptance.</string>
    <string id="whyToan_p2">Years later, this name acquired a new dimension when my partner started using "Toan" affectionately, without knowing the story from when I was a child. This coincidence confirmed its meaning for me: the name now symbolizes a path of constant support, trust, and fidelity.</string>
    <string id="whyToan_p3_intro">In the professional context, Toan becomes the voice of my brand and the pillar of my value proposition:</string>
    <string id="whyToan_list_acompaniment_title">Promise of accompaniment:</string>
    <string id="whyToan_list_acompaniment_text">When Someone needs to comply with digital accessibility in the digitalization process, Toan promises that the client will not have to face the legal and technical complexity alone, but will be guided by a close relationship and mutual support.</string>
    <string id="whyToan_list_force_title">Strength and distinction:</string>
    <string id="whyToan_list_force_text">This orthographic singularity and its strong sonority help the brand stand out visually and be easily remembered in an environment often saturated with generic or overly formal names.</string>
    <string id="whyToan_p4">Toan is, therefore, more than a name; it is a declaration of trust, a commitment that profitable Accessibility will be delivered with the same care and support found in the most significant personal relationships.</string>

    <string id="diference_title">What sets me apart?</string>
    <string id="diference_p1_intro">My difference is my hybrid profile (UX/UI, front-end developer, and specialized digital accessibility profile) and my 360° product vision. When a client hires me, they are not just buying a graphic deliverable (the prototype), but the guarantee of an efficient end-to-end process (the solution). The added value I deliver is twofold:</string>
    <string id="diference_list_garantia_title">Frictionless compliance guarantee:</string>
    <string id="diference_list_garantia_text">My designs inherently include Frontend logic, as well as compliance with accessibility criteria, semantic naming, wai-aria tags, and QA checking from the design phase.</string>
    <string id="diference_list_costos_title">Technical cost reduction:</string>
    <string id="diference_list_costos_text">This integration drastically reduces iterations and errors between design and development teams, which translates into quantifiable savings in the total public project budget. Accessibility becomes a source of efficiency, not an expense.</string>

    <string id="jobs_title">What is my trajectory?</string>
    <string id="job_indra_h3">Senior UX designer</string>
    <string id="job_indra_p">Software design in the field of &lt;strong&gt;aerospace aeronautics.&lt;/strong&gt;</string>
    <string id="job_ecityclic_h3">UX designer &amp; Frontend developer</string>
    <string id="job_ecityclic_p">Design of web and app platforms for the main &lt;strong&gt;public administrations&lt;/strong&gt; of Catalonia, Spain, and Andorra</string>
    <string id="job_qsoft_h3">Fullstack developer</string>
    <string id="job_qsoft_p">Fullstack programmer in &lt;strong&gt;hospital management&lt;/strong&gt; software</string>

    <string id="academy_title">What studies do I have?</string>
    <string id="acad_uoc_h3">Bachelor's Degree in Design and Digital Creation</string>
    <string id="acad_uoc_p">Open University of Catalonia</string>
    <string id="acad_ucam_prog_h3">University Diploma in Advanced Programming</string>
    <string id="acad_ucam_prog_p">Catholic University San Antonio of Murcia</string>
    <string id="acad_ucam_anal_h3">University Diploma in Software Analysis and Design</string>
    <string id="acad_ucam_anal_p">Catholic University San Antonio of Murcia</string>
    <string id="acad_ilerna_daw_h3">Higher Vocational Training in Web Application Development</string>
    <string id="acad_ilerna_daw_p">Ilerna Training</string>
    <string id="acad_ilerna_dam_h3">Higher Vocational Training in Multiplatform Application Development</string>
    <string id="acad_ilerna_dam_p">Ilerna Training</string>
    <string id="acad_ilerna_3d_h3">Higher Vocational Training in 3D Animation, Games, and Interactive Environments</string>
    <string id="acad_ilerna_3d_p">Ilerna Training</string>

    <string id="lang_title">What languages do I speak?</string>
    <string id="lang_ca">Catalan</string>
    <string id="lang_es">Spanish</string>
    <string id="lang_en">English</string>
    <string id="lang_ja">Japanese</string>    
    <string id="lang_ca_p">It is my native language. It would be the equivalent of &lt;strong&gt;C1&lt;/strong&gt;.</string>
    <string id="lang_es_p">It is my native language. It would be the equivalent of &lt;strong&gt;C1&lt;/strong&gt;.</string>
    <string id="lang_en_p">With the university degree, I have acquired the equivalent of &lt;strong&gt;B2&lt;/strong&gt;.</string>
    <string id="lang_ja_p">Beginner level, I am preparing for the &lt;strong&gt;N5&lt;/strong&gt;.</string>
    <string id="challenges_title">Featured Solutions</string>
<string id="challenges_description">What I can show are the main challenges for which I found a useful solution.</string>

<string id="challenge_1_h3">&lt;h3&gt;Cool portfolio&lt;/h3&gt;</string>
<string id="challenge_1_description">Working on top-secret projects (aerospace and public administration) means much of my work is confidential. The challenge was how to demonstrate my &lt;strong&gt;UX, UI, Front-End, and Accessibility&lt;/strong&gt; skills without showing embargoed screens. The solution couldn't be a simple theoretical mockup; it had to be a &lt;strong&gt;live and accessible product&lt;/strong&gt;.</string>
<string id="challenge_1_h4_obstacle">What was the roadblock?</string>
<string id="challenge_1_obstacle_p1">The market is often based on showing the "what" (the final result), but not the "how" (the process and ingenuity). My frustration was that I couldn't convey the technical depth behind each confidential solution. I needed a canvas to show not just a beautiful design, but &lt;strong&gt;functional, accessible, and bold code&lt;/strong&gt;.</string>
<string id="challenge_1_h4_fix">And how did I fix it?</string>
<string id="challenge_1_fix_p1">I created this very portfolio portal as my most ambitious project: a &lt;strong&gt;functional example built from scratch&lt;/strong&gt; that demonstrates my competencies at the highest level.</string>
<string id="challenge_1_ol_li1_h4">Accessibility advocate</string>
<string id="challenge_1_ol_li1_p">This portal complies with the &lt;strong&gt;WCAG Triple AAA&lt;/strong&gt; accessibility level, in both light and dark modes. This is a strong statement of my priority for inclusive design.</string>
<string id="challenge_1_ol_li2_h4">The promise of the unique experience:</string>
<string id="challenge_1_ol_li2_p">To demonstrate the power of my accessible color palette generator, &lt;strong&gt;every time the portal loads&lt;/strong&gt;, a completely new primary color is generated, and from that, a unique accessible palette is built. This conveys that my approach to the end-user (and to you) will always be &lt;strong&gt;unique and exclusive&lt;/strong&gt;.</string>
<string id="challenge_1_ol_li3_h4">The challenge of originality:</string>
<string id="challenge_1_ol_li3_p">I identify with the Japanese mindset: if someone has done it, I can also learn to do it; but if no one has done it, I must be the first to achieve it. This portfolio is my proof that I actively seek to overcome known boundaries.</string>
<string id="challenge_1_h4_result">Result and the fear of sharing:</string>
<string id="challenge_1_result_p1">&lt;strong&gt;Am I afraid to make the code for my tools public?&lt;/strong&gt; The answer is a resounding &lt;strong&gt;No&lt;/strong&gt;.</string>
<string id="challenge_1_result_p2">My goal is twofold: first, to &lt;strong&gt;show what I can do&lt;/strong&gt; and how I face challenges. And second, to &lt;strong&gt;foster accessibility&lt;/strong&gt;. If someone uses my code as a reference point, I feel proud. And if someone improves it, they'll be showing me that I still have much to learn.</string>
<string id="challenge_1_result_p3">This portfolio is a &lt;strong&gt;manifesto of humility and ambition&lt;/strong&gt;: a solid foundation for creating superior and 100% accessible user experiences.</string>

<string id="challenge_2_h3">&lt;h3&gt;Accessible contrast checker&lt;/h3&gt;</string>
<string id="challenge_2_description">Everyone knows they must comply with WCAG standards, but the reality is that a single contrast error forces recalculating the entire palette (dark variants, light variants, hover states...) in a slow process full of potential manual errors. We needed a tool that would give us speed, consistency, and reliability in a demanding environment like aerospace and administration.</string>
<string id="challenge_2_h4_obstacle">What was the roadblock?</string>
<string id="challenge_2_obstacle_p1">There are many contrast calculators on the market, but they all limit themselves to saying "Does not comply" or "Does comply." The problem was the effort the design and development teams had to invest after the error message.</string>
<string id="challenge_2_obstacle_p2">The goal was not only to validate but to propose the solution at the same moment. We had to go further to eliminate the trial and error loop from our work.</string>
<string id="challenge_2_h4_fix">And how did I fix it?</string>
<string id="challenge_2_fix_p1">I decided to develop my own autonomous tool. This contrast check functions as an &lt;strong&gt;Integral Palette Assistant&lt;/strong&gt;, and not just a simple calculator:</string>
<string id="challenge_2_ol_li1_h4">Intelligent Verification:</string>
<string id="challenge_2_ol_li1_p">Shows the real contrast and allows selecting the required WCAG standard (A, AA, or AAA) with a simple level selector.</string>
<string id="challenge_2_ol_li2_h4">Automatic Correction:</string>
<string id="challenge_2_ol_li2_p">If the ratio fails, the tool automatically suggests the color most similar to the original that does comply with the requested standard.</string>
<string id="challenge_2_ol_li3_h4">Full Palette Generation:</string>
<string id="challenge_2_ol_li3_p">From the corrected main color, the tool instantly generates the complete accessible palette (main color, contrast color, dark/light variants) and the minimum necessary variations for all components to be accessible on light and dark backgrounds.</string>
<string id="challenge_2_h4_result">Result:</string>
<string id="challenge_2_result_p1">Not only did we guarantee legal compliance and accessibility without room for error, but we saved hours of work, as the tool delivers a ready-to-code palette that the developer can implement directly.</string>
<string id="challenge_2_link_text">Contrast checker</string>
<string id="challenge_2_link_title">Go to the Contrast checker tool. Opens in a new tab.</string>

<string id="challenge_3_h3">&lt;h3&gt;Responsive table&lt;/h3&gt;</string>
<string id="challenge_3_description">Complex data tables are an eternal challenge in mobile design. The quick option is &lt;strong&gt;horizontal scroll&lt;/strong&gt;, but this is not only a bad experience (UX) but often &lt;strong&gt;invalidates the WCAG 1.4.10 (Reflow) guideline&lt;/strong&gt;, forcing the user to move in two dimensions. For administration projects, where data clarity is crucial, we need solutions that are &lt;strong&gt;100% accessible and visually superior&lt;/strong&gt;.</string>
<string id="challenge_3_h4_obstacle">What was the roadblock?</string>
<string id="challenge_3_obstacle_p1">The main obstacle was maintaining the &lt;strong&gt;semantic context&lt;/strong&gt; of each data point when the table transformed. In the mobile view, the user loses the column title reference, making the reading of complex data inefficient and frustrating.</string>
<string id="challenge_3_obstacle_p2">In addition, most solutions rely on a Media Query based on the &lt;strong&gt;screen size&lt;/strong&gt;, which is invalid when the table is in a narrow container, breaking the modularity of the design.</string>
<string id="challenge_3_h4_fix">And how did I fix it?</string>
<string id="challenge_3_fix_p1">I implemented an intelligent front-end solution, converting each table row into a &lt;strong&gt;vertical card&lt;/strong&gt; in the mobile view. This solution is not only more visual but also guarantees data accessibility:</string>
<string id="challenge_3_ol_li1_h4">Semantic enrichment with data-Labels:</string>
<string id="challenge_3_ol_li1_p">To each data cell, I added a &lt;code&gt;data-label=""&lt;/code&gt; attribute containing the original column title. This ensures the semantic relationship is not lost and remains accessible to screen readers.</string>
<string id="challenge_3_ol_li2_h4">Container-based Transformation:</string>
<string id="challenge_3_ol_li2_p">Instead of relying on the global viewport, I used &lt;strong&gt;Container Queries&lt;/strong&gt; (&lt;code&gt;@container&lt;/code&gt;). Thus, the table detects the actual width of its container (&lt;code&gt;.responsive-table-wrapper&lt;/code&gt;) and only transforms when the space is reduced.</string>
<string id="challenge_3_ol_li3_h4">Modular Visualization:</string>
<string id="challenge_3_ol_li3_p">In the small view, each row transforms into a block (display: flex; flex-direction: column;). The column title is inserted as a pseudoelement (&lt;code&gt;td::before&lt;/code&gt;) using the content of the &lt;code&gt;data-label&lt;/code&gt;, offering a clear and linear reading experience.</string>
<string id="challenge_3_h4_result">Result:</string>
<string id="challenge_3_result_p1">I complied with the WCAG Reflow standard and provided a superior user experience, eliminating the need for lateral sliding. The implementation with &lt;strong&gt;Container Queries&lt;/strong&gt; ensures this table is 100% modular and consistent in any layout context.</string>
<string id="challenge_3_table_responsive_heading_actions">Actions</string>

<string id="challenge_4_h3">&lt;h3&gt;System variables&lt;/h3&gt;</string>
<string id="challenge_4_description">Working with multiple clients and products (especially in administration) means a constant struggle to maintain &lt;strong&gt;visual consistency&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;development efficiency&lt;/strong&gt;. The great challenge is to create unique and distinctive designs for each branding without having to design and code every component from scratch. We needed a single CSS code base that could serve multiple products.</string>
<string id="challenge_4_h4_obstacle">What was the roadblock?</string>
<string id="challenge_4_obstacle_p1">Before this solution, customizing a new portal required the direct intervention of a design team to change colors, spacing, and typography, generating &lt;strong&gt;duplicate CSS&lt;/strong&gt; and a high risk of inconsistencies. Any modification or change in requirements (such as increasing the accessibility level) was costly and slow, as it had to be applied manually to each product file.</string>
<string id="challenge_4_h4_fix">And how did I fix it?</string>
<string id="challenge_4_fix_p1">I created a &lt;strong&gt;Modular Layout System&lt;/strong&gt; based on &lt;strong&gt;CSS Variables&lt;/strong&gt; (or Design Tokens). This system allows for the complete customization of a portal or application's appearance directly from the HTML, without touching the base CSS.</string>
<string id="challenge_4_ol_li1_h4">Total modularization with variables:</string>
<string id="challenge_4_ol_li1_p">All main CSS (colors, spacing, text sizes, border-radius) was modularized using &lt;strong&gt;CSS variables&lt;/strong&gt;. This means that the functionality (e.g., a button) is the same, but its visual style depends on a few lines of code.</string>
<string id="challenge_4_ol_li2_h4">On-the-fly customization:</string>
<string id="challenge_4_ol_li2_p">Customization is done by adding a few classes to the &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;body&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; tag (e.g., &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;body class="contenedor-full font-serif radius-smooth font-combo-1"&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;). These classes simply &lt;strong&gt;override&lt;/strong&gt; the values of the global CSS variables, changing the appearance of the entire website.</string>
<string id="challenge_4_ol_li3_h4">Accessibility by default:</string>
<string id="challenge_4_ol_li3_p">This architecture ensures that, regardless of the selected token combination, the system always maintains the &lt;strong&gt;minimum accessibility levels&lt;/strong&gt; required by public administration (contrasts, font sizes) by default.</string>
<string id="challenge_4_h4_result">Result:</string>
<string id="challenge_4_result_p1">I achieved &lt;strong&gt;extreme scalability&lt;/strong&gt;. A developer or designer can select the layout, typography, rounding, and margins of a new portal in a matter of minutes. We went from designing to &lt;strong&gt;configuring&lt;/strong&gt;, saving hours of design and development on every new project, with the added guarantee of consistent accessibility.</string>
<string id="challenge_4_link_text">System variables</string>
<string id="challenge_4_link_title">Go to the System variables tool. Opens in a new tab.</string>
<string id="skill_advanced_1">UX Design</string>
<string id="skill_advanced_2">Accessibility</string>
<string id="skill_advanced_3">UI Design</string>
<string id="skill_advanced_4">Front-End Development</string>
<string id="skill_advanced_5">Layout Architecture</string>
<string id="skill_advanced_6">Design Systems</string>
<string id="skill_advanced_7">Problem Solving</string>
<string id="skill_advanced_8">Information Architecture</string>
<string id="skill_advanced_9">Prototyping and Interface Validation</string>
<string id="skill_advanced_10">Confidentiality Management</string>
<string id="skill_advanced_11">UX Writing</string>
<string id="projects_more_desc">What I can show you is what I really enjoy: the engineering and accessibility challenges I've faced, and how I've solved them with creative and robust solutions. If there's an obstacle, I look for the best solution!</string>
<string id="projects_solutions">View featured challenges</string>
</translations>